{
    "id": "3b11042ef00c423e9b51b01f4cecf377",
    "title": "Affirmative To Negative",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My sister ....................................... not live with my parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e70eb5750f624a0e9de95780a32895f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. not know the answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4d9de0511d2d422ab61f856f5db3d669"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ not want to leave now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "97c91365a51748c0930cb149d3312bcf"
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother ........................................... not work at a bank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6bdfaf64caf4520894dfc3ccd3ebfd9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Supriya ............................................... not sing very well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c0397023f30e474db1ed086858f2b482"
        },
        {
            "question": "Martin .................................................. not get along with his brother-in-law.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b27c388ad62f4265af9dd61b11a5d81c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy .............................................. not kill the spider with his shoe.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "55cb17400a364ab6afa660e9e47ac4e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .................................... not recognize him at once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2dd5a1afb7af47dbaa4672bd4457b1be"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................................... not apologize for his conduct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "170769a96a4a48e1a1ed0350c2b7e74d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .............................................. not throw a tantrum when she was told that she wouldnâ€™t be able to go.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4959f1a1409644869259c6825db6e7ca"
        }
    ]
}